1. Back. Bow. Bood. Bic. Beak. Book. Beck. Bake. Buck. Bok. Berk. Bark. Boat. Bite.
Point. 2. Black. Blouse. Blewed. Bliss. Bleed. Books. Bled. Blade. Blood. Block.
Blurred. Blarney. Bloat. Blight. Boy. 3. Brad, browse, brood, brick, breed, brook,
bred, break, brother, brought, fur, far, broke, bright, broil, for, pat, about,
boot, pit, peak, put, pet, paid, putt, pot, pert, part, post, pike, boil, five,
cat, couch, coot, kit, parakeet, cookie, kept, cate, cut, Kurt, cart, coat, kite,
coin, six, cad, cowed, cooed, kid, keyed, could, keds, okayed, cud, cod, curd, card,
code, cried, coil, seven, fat, found, food, fit, Feet. Foot. Fed. Fade. Fun.
Fog. First. Farm. Phone. Fight. Foit. Ate. Flak. Flower. Fluke. Flick. Fleet. Put.
FLEC, FLAKE, FLOOD, FATHER, FLURRY, FAR, TAR, FLOW, FLIGHT, FLOID. 9. FRAGIL,
FROWN, FRUIT, FRILL, FREE, FRUCTOSE, FRENCH, AFRAID, FROM, FROG, FURTHER,
FARTHER, fro, fright, Freud, ten, fallow, foul, fool, fill, feel, full, fell, fail,
fuss, fall, FURL, CARL, PHOTO, FILE, FOIL 11. GAS, GOUT, GOOD, GIVE, GEAK, GOOD,
GET, GATE, GUN, GONE, GERD, GARD, GOAD, GUIDE, GOITER 12. Catch. Couch. Cool.
Kick. Key. Cook. Catch. Cake. Come. Calm. Kirk. Carp. Coal. Kind. Coy. 13. Lack.
Loud. Luke. Lick. Leak. Look. Lecture. Lake. Luck. Lock. Lurk. Lark. Local. Like.
Lawyer. 14. Mallet. Mound. Mood. Mill. Meal. Wooden. Men. Main. Mother. Mom.
Murmur. March. Mobile. Mile. Des Moines. 15. PAL, POWEL, POOL, PILL, PEEL, PULL,
PELL, PALE, PUCK, POCK, PEARL, PARK, POLL, PILE, POISON. 16. Sand. Sound. Soon. Sin.
Seen. Soot. Send. Same. Some. Son. Sir. Sorry. sewn, sign, soil. 17. Satin,
mountain, gluten, mitten, eaten, wooden, retina, latent, button, gotten, certain,
carton, potent, titan, ointment. 18. Shad, shout, shoed, shick, sheet, should, shed,
shade, shun, shop, insured, sharp, show, 19. Shack. Shower. Shoed. Shiver. Sheik.
Shook. Chef. Shake. Shuck. Shock. Shirt. Shark. Shows. 20. Shallow. Shower. Shoot.
Shift. Sheep. Sugar. Shell. Shale. Shut. Shot. Shurer. Shard. Shone. Shine. 21.
Chance. Chowder. Choose. Chin. Cheek. Chest. Change. Chuck. Chalk. Churn.
Charge. chose, child, choice, twenty-two, tack, towel, two, tick, teak, took, tech,
take, tuck, talk, turkey, tarp, toke, tyke, toy, 23, that, thousand, through,
this, these, then, they, The. Thought. Third. Cathartic. Though. Thy. Thyroid.
24. Had. Howed. Hoed. Hid. Heed. Hood. Hen. Hate. Hud. Hod. Heard. Hard. Hoed.
Hyde. Hoi Ploy. 25. Hat. About. Hoot. Hit. Heat. Foot. Heck. Hague. Hut. Hot. Hurt.
Heart. Hotel. Height. Hoyle. 26. Value. Vow. Review. Villain. Reveal. Vegetable.
Vague. Vogue. Vaughn. Verve. Varnish. vile, avoid, 27, whack, wow, wooed, wick,
weak, wood, wed, wade, what, walk, word, harm, woke, White. Woy.